Guide to the Fedor Stepun Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Fingerle, Anton
Fink, Brigitte
Finkbeiner-Eppe, Annemarie
Fischer Bucherei Frankfurt am Main (S. Fischer Verlag?)
Fischer, Herbert
Fischer, Ilse (cf. Heilbronner Stimme)
Fischer, Leonard
Fischer, Wolfgang
Fisher, Berta
Fisher, Nikolai
Flab-Lichtenberg, L.
Flügel, Heinz
Foelkersahm, Hamilkar Baron
Folkwangschule der Stadt Essen
Forchhammer, J.
Forster, ?
Forster, Dirk
Förster, George
Forsthoff, Ernst
Fortbildungsausschauss (J. Songen)
Forum
Foss, Bernhard
Franck, Werner
Franckh, Hans-Heinz
Franke, Karl H.
Frankfurter Rundschau
Die Frau
Frauenring Bayern
Frauenstein, G. von
Frederiks, Baron B. V.
Free Europe Citizens Service
Frei-Belotsvetova, Elena
Freie Rundschau
Freie und Hansestadt Hamburg
Freies Europa
Freiwirtschaftsbund
Freisburger, W.
Freistudentenschaft Bern
Freizeitgemeinschaft Siemens München
Fremery, Natasha and Walter
Freunde der Bildenden Kunst
Freunde der Residenz
Freunde der "Stätte der Begegnung"
Freudenberg, A.
Freundenfeld, Gurghard
Fr. Frommann Verlag
Friedmann, ?
Friedrich Bassermann Verlag
Friedrich-Ebert-Stiftung
Frieson, Nina von
Friessner, Hans
Friengs, ?
Fritsch, Alexander von
Fritson, ?
Fritze, Wolfgang
Fritzsche, Ursula
Fröchtling, August
Frucht, Hans (with photograph)
Füll, Gertrude
Funk, Klaus
Fürstenberg, Ferd. Frhr. von
Furtwängler, Margaret
Gabriel, M.
Gaceta ilustrada
Gaede, ?
Gagarin, Evgenii
Gagarin, R., Fürst
Gahlnbäck-Wolff, Marita
Galerie Wolfgang Gurlitt (München)
Gallinger, Elsa
Gapanovich, J. J.
Garmaschoff, Georg W.
Gärtner, Eleonore
Gatschike, Horst
Gebhardt, Franz
Gebhardt-Leele, F.
Gebirgsjägerbataillon 232
Gebsattel, V. E. von
GEDOK
Gehrig, Marie and Hans
Geilen, Vitalis
Geislingen an der Steige
Geist und Freiheit
Gemen-Komitee (Franz Berning)
Genzsch, A.
Geppert, Lotte
Georg-August Universität
Georgiades, J.
Geppert, Lotte
Gerecke, H.
Gerhardt, Dietrich
Gerloff, H.
Gershel'man, E.
Gerstacker, W. (Frankische Kreis)
Geschichte in Wissenschaft und Unterricht
Gesek, Ludwig
Gesellschaft christliches Abenland
Gesellschaft der Biedermeier Baden
Gesellschaft der Bücherfreunde zu Hamburg
Gesellschaft für christliche Kultur Würzburg
Gesellschaft Imshausen
Gicklleorn (?), Walter
Gilbert, O
Gilde (Bayerischer Krankenversicherungsverein?)
Giler, L
Gillianth, K.
Girgenson, B
Giterman, Valentin
Glantz, Wolfgang
Glassen, E.
Gleerapska Universitetsbokhandeln
Glimm, Gesine???
Glogger, Charlotte
Glogowski, Paul
Goarind (?), Rudolf
Goethebund Delmenhorst
Goldenweiser, A. A. (Aleksei Aleksandrovich)
Goldhammer, Regina
Goldschmidt-Jentner, Rudolf R.
Goldvin, T.
Goncharov, N.
Gordienko, N. G.
Gordon, Edmund von
Gordonov, Andrei
Gorny, A.
Gorte, Gertrud
Gorte, Ludwig
Gotthelf-Verlag
Gottschalk, H. L.
Gouvernment Militaire de la Zone Francaise d'Occupation
Grabert, W.
Grabis, Th.
Grägor, Arthur
Gras, Marion
Gregorius Verlag
Greifenhagen, Helmuth
Gremm, Alfred
Grenel
Greve, Rolf
Grimm, Elisabeth
Grimm, Heinrich
Groetschel, Johannes
Groezinger, Anne
Groh, Hella
Gropp, K.
Gross, ?? (Frau)
Gross, Werner
Grossmann, Felizitas
Grossmann, Paul
Grote, Ludwig
Gruber, Theodor
Gruner, L.
Grüzinger, W.
Guerard, Nikolas von
Guillemin, Bernard
Guirten, E.
Guislar, F.
Gumppenberg, Herr von
Gundermann, Fritz
Günther, Herbert
Gunthof, Mayer
Gunzberger, Elsbeth
Gunzert, Gertrude Barbara
Haas, A. de
Habermann, Willi
Habbel, Josef, Jr.
Hache, R.
Hadrossek, P.
Hagemann, Walter
Hagemeister, Heinz von
Hagen (City)
Hagen, Rainer
Hahn, Fr.
Hahn, Hans-Peter
Hahn, Josef
Hall, Maria
Haller, Rudolf
Halm, Hans
Hamberger, Rudolf
Hamburg, Else
Hamburger akademische Rundschau
Hamburger öffentliche Bücherhallen
Hamm, Martl
Handbuch der Weltgeschichte
Handwerberei Rohi
Hänel, Gerhard (Handwerberei)
Hanfsler, H.
Hannoversche Allgemeine
Hannoversche Hochschule
Hannoversche Presse
Hanns W. Brose GMBH & Co.
Hans, ?
Hans Bredow-Institut
Hans Schwarz Verlag
Hansen, Kurt Heinrich
Harder, Johannes
Harten, R. von
Hartenback, Walter
Hartig, H. A.
Harting, J.
Hartmann, Arthur
Hartmann, Heinrich
Hartmann, Kurt and Lore (in re Meta Gadesmann)
Hasinger, Fritz
Hassmann, Heinrich
Hasting, ? (Frau)
Hattemer, Magdl
Hauffe, Hans Cruntes (?)
Haus Adlerberg
Hauska, Maria
Haussmann, Wilhelm
Haut-Commissariat de la République Française en Allemagne
Hawel, Gerhard
Hechtz, M.
Heckel, D. Theodor (Dean of ??, q.v.)
Hederer, Oswald
Heerwagen, Alfred
Hegele, Gotthold
Hegemann, Ferdinand
Hehn, Peter
Heidelberger Kulturbund
Heidenberger, P. and A.
Heidt, H.
Heiduschka, Hans-Georg
Heidrich, ? H. (Hannover Landesbund; Stadttheater Lubeck)
Heike, O.
Heimann, Eduard
Heinrichs, P.
Heinz Ullstein-Helmut Kindler Verlag
Helkenberg, Nina
Hellmann, Rudolf
Helmes, Fromund
Hengstenberg, H. E.
Hennig, Arno
Hennig, Helmut
Hennig, Johann
Henschel, Bien[art]
Hentrich, Konrad
Herbert Rothmayer
Herdersche Buchhandlung München
Herdes, Walter
Herrmann, Johanna
Herrschel, Christoph
Hess, Willi
Hessen, Johannes
Hessische Minister für Erziehung und Volksbildung
Hessischer Rundfunk
Hessische Verlagsanstalt
Heubl, Franz
Heute
Heymann, P. Otto
Hickenlooper, ??
Hien, Hans
Hierling, Sebastian
Higgin, Egon
High Commissioner for Refugees
Hildebrandt, Erica
Hilf, Rudolf
Hilger, Gustav (re Tolstoy Found.)
Hilger, W.
Hilsberg, H. Christoph
Hirschhorn, Hans
Hirtz, Wilhelm
Hitzer, Friedrich
Hlynowski, G. von
Hoffman, Elle
Hoffman, Florenz von
Hoffman, Johanna
Hoffman, T. F.
Hoffminden, ?
Hofmann, Michael
Hog, Hugo
Hogrege, B.
Holl, Adolf
Holldack, Maria
Holle Verlag (Darmstadt)
Hollerer, Walter
Holst, Walter
Holtbecker, Carl
Holthaus, K.
Holytschinskyi, A.
Honigsheim, Paul
Hoppe, Gisela
Hörmann, Wolfgang
Hornitz, Kurt
Hornuf, J.
Huber, Anton
Hugendubel, H.
Hüllenbrandt, Theo
Humberger, Rudolf
Hurtienne, Gerlind
Hurwig, E.
IAkovlenko, B.
IAkubenko, V.
IAnitskii
IAnkovskii, Petr
IAnov, B
Ilh, Friedrich
Ilten, Frau von
Im Schreibabtal des F. (Wölker)
Industrie-Club Dusseldorf (Biebrach)
Informations Dienst Moralische Aufrüstung
Insel Verlag (F. Arnold; S. Campe)
Institut für Auslandsbeziehungen
Institut für den Unterrichtsfilm
Institut für Kultur und Sozialforschung
Institut für Physiologie und Ernährung der Tierede Univ. München
Institut für Rechstphilosophie und Rechtspsychologie
Institut für politische Wissenschaft
Institut für Staatslehre und Politik
Institut für Völkerverständigung Coburg
Institut für Wissenschaftliche Filme
Intendanz der Bayerischen Staatsoper
Intergovernmental Committee on Refugees (E. R. Mirkovich)
International Christian Press and Information Service (Geneva)
International Commission of Jurists
Internationale christliche Studenten Vereinigung (YMCA)
Internationale Seminar
Internationale Theaterwoche der Studentbuhnen
Internationale Woche "Film und Universität" (Eberhard Hauff)
Internationaler Arbeitskreis Sonnenberg
Internationaler Kongress für Philosophie der Wissenschaften
Internationaler Studentenbund ISSF
Internationaler Studentenclub München
Internationales Insitut
Interreport Presse-Agentur
Irgizov, N
Isar Verlag
Isenstead, Erich W.
Istituto Italiano di cultura
Italiaander, Rolf
Itter, Edith
IUganson, Lidiia Andreevna
IUkker, S. and E.
Ivanovsky, E.N.
Iwand, Hans
Jablonski, Nil
Jacobs, Horst
Jacobs Jürgen
Jacobsen, Otto
Jacques Ronsenthal Buch- und Kunstantiquariat
Jaeger, Manfred
Jakimow, Maria
Jansen, Fritljof
Janssen, Karl
Jantsch, Walther
Jering, Karl
J. Fink Verlag
Jochen, Hans
Jodl, L.
Johann Gottfried-Herder Institut
Johannes König Buch- und Kunsthanddlung
Johannes Stauda-Verlag
John, Erich
Joint Services School for Linguistics
Jonas, Edmund
Joschkowitz, Isa
J.P. Toth Verlag
Jugendaufbauwerk
Jugendleiterschule
Jugendsozialwerk
Juhr, Hans-Joachim
Jülich (City)
Jull, Jean
Jung, A.E.
Jung, Gerhard
Junge Unternehmer
J.W. Christopher Publishing Company
Kadach, Dorothea
Kaden-Frauckenkain (?), Irmgard
Kadomtsev, B (Russkaia Pravda)
Kadruf Kasseler Druckerei und Färberei
Kaferstrasse, die Leuten von der
Kafka, Gustav
Kägel, Willy
Kahmann, H.
Kairos (M. Vereno)
Kaiser, Aranka
Kakliugin, F. V. (Kaklügin)
Kalinintschuk, Nikolaus
Kalhoff, Angelika
Kammüller, ?
Kampmann, Theoderich
Kandl, Hanna
Kanitz, G.
Kanz, Heinrich
Karakabenko (?), Arkadii Gerasimovich
Karl Rauch Verlag
Kassianeum
Kästner, Erhart
Kastner, Trude
Katholiken-Ausschuss der Stadt Dusseldorf
Katolische deutsche Studenten-Verbindung Tuiskonia (Jürgen Kuchenwald)
Katholische Kulturgemeinde (Bad Homburg)
Katholische Kulturgemeinde Nürnberg)
Katholische Pfarrgemeinde St. Marien
Katholische Studentengemeinde (Bonn)
Katholische Studentengemeinde (Münster)
Katholische Studentenseelsorge an der Universität Tubingen
Katholische Studenten-Verbindung Südmark
Katholische Studenten-Verein Ottonia
Katholische Studenten-Verein Saxonia
Katholische studierende Jugend. Bund Neudeutschland. Hochschulring
Katholische Wissenschaftliche Studenten-Verbindung
Katholisches Bildungswerk (Saarland)
Katholisches Bildungswerk Tirol
Katholisches Kulturwerk Schweinfurt
Katholisches Männerwerk (Marienheide) (G. Miesbach)
Katholisches Stadtpfarramt St. Moritz
Kattchee, Peter v.
Katzmann-Verlag-Tübingen
Kauffmann, Elfriede
Kauffmann, Wilhelm
Kaufmännischer Verein
Kaum, Ludwig
Keil, Rolf-Dietrich
Keim, Walter (Bayer Staatsminister für Untericht und Kultur
Kell, M.
Keller, Hans K.E.L.
Keller, Peter
Keller, Wolfgang
Keller, ?
Kellerer, C.
Kelley, Robert
Kempe, F.
Kerschkamp, Renate
Kessler, ?
Kienast, Hansjuergen
Kienast, Ulrich
Kiener, Franz
Kijsltra, R. W.
Killing, Otto
Kimental', N.V.
Kindersley, Richard
Kinz, Franziska
Kirchhoff, Fritz
Kirchhoff, Peterheinrich
Kirchliches Aussenamt der Evangelical Kirche in Deutschland
Kirillov, V. I.
Kirschmer, Otto
Kirschstein, Helmut
Kläschen, ?
Klatt, L.
Klein, B.
Klein, Emmy
Klein, Ruth
Klimenko, Michael
Klingler, Norbert
Klockmann, Egon
Klopstock-Stiftung, (Greta?)
Kluge, E.
Klugert, ??
Knapp, Werner
Knellessen, F. Wolf
Knoblauch-Faure, Amanda
Knüfer, Ema
Koch, Elisabeth
Koch, Fritz
Koch, Sophie
Koch, Walter
Kochubei, B. (Kotschubey)
Koehler und Volckmar
Koestel, Walter
Köhler, Selma
Kohlhammer Verlag (Heiss)
Kolchak, A. (Alexander Koltschak)
Kolitsch, Anna
Kolmaigmer, Mitzi
Kolme, Marie
Köln (Germany) Kölner Zeitschrift für Soziologie Kölnische Braunkohlen-Centrale
Koltschak, Catherine
Komerwerell (?), Erika
Komitee der garmischer Hochschulwoche
Komitee "Rettet die Freiheit"
Komitet po izdaniiu posmertnogo truda P.B. Struve
Komitet po organizatsii Dnia Russkoi Kul'tury
Komitet po uchastii Rossiiskikh Emigrantov
Komitet "Za povernennia na Bat'kivshchynu"
Komma
Komödie
Kompass-Verlag
Köngener Kreis
Kongress für die Freiheit der Kultur
König, Horst Jörg
Kopuk, Marz
Korndorfer, K.
Kornhardt, Hildegard
Kornilii, Igumen (Hegumen)
Kornhardt, Hildegard
Kosnick, Heinrich
Köster, G.
Kotsovsky, D.
Kovalev, I. F.
Kozintseva-Durnova, V.
Kracht, Elisabeth
Kracht, F. A.
Kraemer, Otto
Kraeht, Elisabeth
Kraft, Bernhard
Krahmer, Kate Sch.
Kramann, Johann
Krannhals, Hanns von
Krasboers (?), Fr. von
Kratsch, Charlotte
Kratz, Dr.
Krause, Erich
Krause, Herbert
Krausskopf, Otto K.
Kreher-Wunsch, Annemarie
Kreis für Kultur und Kunst
Kreisjugendpfleger
Kreisvolkshockschule Siegerland
Kremsreiter, Johanna
Kresling, Alexander
Kressner, A.
Krestovskaia, Lidiia Aleksandrovna
Kreutzkam, Joachim
Kreuz-Verlag Stuttgart
Krieser?, H.
Kripton, Konstantin Georgievich
Krivenko, G.
Kröhnke, Erich
Kroll, Gerhard
Krotkova, Khristina Pavlovna
Krummhaar, Herbert von
Kruse, Alfred
Krymov, V.
Kuchta, Martin
Kuen, H.
Kuhlmann, H. (Information Centre Recklinghausen. Engelsburg)
Kuhn, Helmut
Kühn, Herbert
Kuhn, K.
Kuhn, Martin
Kühn, Rose
Kuhn, ?
Kulmir, Christine
Kulturausschuss für Lohr und Umbegung
Kulturbund Hof
Kulturdezernat Stadtverwaltung Göttingen
Kulturgemeinde Stolberg (Klemens Freiburg-Rüter)
Kulturkreis Fischbachau-Aurach
Kulturkreis Gummersbach
Kulturkreis Rottach-Egern
Kulturkreis Waldtrudering
Kulturkreise Schliersee und Neuhaus
Kulturliga
Kultur und Theatergemeinde Frankfurt
Kulturring Duisburg-Meiderich
Kulturvereinigung Seligenstadt und Umgebung
Kumming, E.
Kunsthalle Basel (R. Th. Stoll)
Künstlergilde (Muhlberger, Josef)
Kunstverein der Diözese Rottenburg
Kupfer, N. A.
Kuratorium Unteilbares Deutschland (Dr. Eulerich)
Kurhessische Gesellschaft fur Kunst un Wissenschaft
Kurt Vowinckel Verlag
Kutyrina, IUliia Aleksandrovna
Lachermair, Ol'ga (Malakhova-Kuchusheva)
Lades, Hans
Lahme, Walter
Laible, Eva
Lainn, Dmitrii
Lambrecht, Anita
Lämmel, Heinrich
Lammerskitten, Klaus
Lampus, M.
Der Landbote
Landers, Hans
Landesen, Frau
Landeskuratorium Bayern fur das Weltflüchtlingsjahr
Landesverband der Volkhochschulen Niederseichsens
Landesverband der Volkhochschulen von Nordrhein-Westfalen
Landkreis Siegen
Landsmannschaft Schliesen
Lang, Hugo
Lang, Paul Langenthaler Tageblatt (Steiner, Ad.)
Lankowsky, Rudolf
Lapin
Lasenfuss, Margarette
Lassalin, Maria de
Lassmann, August Kurt
Lau, Sigrid
Laudsittell, Carola
Laugenberg, Dr.
Laumanns, Max
Lauterbach, Gertrude
L.Boltze Buchhandlung
Ledibur (?), Mario von
Lega della Liberta
Lehmann, Arno
Lehmann, Elfriede
Lehmann, M.
Lehmann, Wilhelm
Leipzig (City)
Lemberg, Eugen
Lemorius, M. R. von
Lenz, Friedrich
Leont'ev, L. A.
Lersche, Ruth & Philip(pe)
Leseverein, E. V. Velbert (Gloga?, Alfred)
Lesezimmer der christlichen Wissenschaft
Lessing-Gesellschaft Nürnberg
Lettemeyer, Lore
Lewis, Richard W.B.
Ley, Eugen von der
Lezius, Friedrich
Liberaler Studentenbund Deutschlands (LSD)
Liberman, M.
Lichel (?), ?
Licht, Alexander
Liebelt, Lev
Lievers (?), M.
Likhosherstov, A. and Lidiia
Lilje, Edith
Limmer, V.
Linderberg, Wladimir (Vladimir Aleksandrovich Lindenberg-Chelishchev)
Linus Manuskriptdienst...
Lions Club International. München
Liozine, V.
Lippert, P.
Lippisch, Gertrud
Literarisch-Dramatische Gesellschaft Langenthal (Steiner, A.)
Literarische Gesellschaft Bochum
LIterarische Gesellschaft Zug
Literarische und Lesegesellschaft (Aarau)
Literaturnyi Fond
Litz, ??
Liubchenko, N.
Liubimov, P.
Liubishchev, Dm.
Loeben, Georg
Loessl, Ottmar von
Loete, Martha
Loewe, Oscar
Loewenstein, ?? (Herr)
Lohmann, G.
Lohmer, Bert
Lohmer, H.
Lorbe, Ruth
Lorenz, J.
Lorka, Blanche
Lotz, Johannes
Lovskaia, ?
Lozina, D. Anna (Isolana)
L. Schwann Druckerei und Verlad (Dusseldorf)
Lübben, Fritz
Ludingham (?), Mara von
Luisk, Eugen
Luther, Ewe Imogen
Luther Verlag
Lutheran World Federation
Lutherhaus Verlag
Luxburg, Heinrich S.
Luyken, Erika
Maas, Eberhard W.
McLeod (Jaeger), Brigitte
Madey, Johannes
Madlung, Maria
Mahler, E.
Maier, Anton
Maier, Hans
Maier, ?
Maikämper, Pfr.
Main-Post
Makarov, Vladimir
Makorski, Ruth
Maksimadzhi
Malbi, ?
Mal'chenko, A.
Mallac, Guy de
Malyoth, Prof.
Mand, Friedl
Manetstätter, Theodora
Manfred, E.
Mangoldt-Reibolt, H. K. von
Mann, Wilhelm
Mann, Wolfgang
Mannheim, Christian
Mannheimer Kultur- und Dokumentar-Filmwoche
Mannte, M
Mantey, ?? von
Mantzke, Martin
Margarete Hasting Schule
Margolin, A.
Margolin, Julius
Marguene, Elisabeth
Margulies, Wilhelm
Marhefka, ?
Marinesen-Baldi, Teresa
Marsenbach-Runge, Annie
Marschka, H.
Martini, Fritz
Martinov, Boris
Martius, Marie-Agnes von
Marwitz, Georg E.
Marx, R.
Maskasek, W.
Matern, Aloys and Anneliese
Mathiesen, Werner
Matt, Rudi
Matthias-Grünewald-Verlag
Mattick, Friedrich
Matushinskaia, Vera
Matveev, Sergii (Protoierei)
Mauch, Erika
Mauk, Marielies
Maul, Friedhild
Maurer, Bernhard
Maurer, ?
Max Policzka Elektro-Installation
Maximillians-Gymnasium
Mayerhofer, Fritz
Meckauer, Walter
Meessen, Karl-Matthias
Meier, Bernhard
Meissinger, K. A.
Meller, Michael
Menrad, Josef
Mentsinger-Stuken, D.
Mentschukoff, Nikolaj (N. Men'chukov)
Metopen-Verlag
Meyer, Elisabeth
Meyer, Erich
Meyer, Hans
Meyer, Paul
Michael Beckstein Verlag
Michalawsky, Nikolai von
Michel, ?
Mikrokopie
Miller, ?
Miller, Hans and Anne von
Miller, Rudolph von
Milner, Emmy (Billarbeck)
Miroschnikoff, Boris (Boris Sergeevich Miroshnikov)
Mitchell, Stanley Der Mittag Model, Arthur
Mohe, Anna
Möhler, Armin
Möhlich, Karl
Molineus (?), Arndt
Molineus, Gerd
Mommsen, Helene Monats Hefte Mönch, Karl
Monzel, Nikolaus
Moralische Aufrüstung
Morell-Krähmer, Käte
Morelli, A.
Morelli, Zinaida
Mörike-Buchhandlung
Morris, Rudolf E. and M.
M.S. Metz Verlag
Mudanov, IAkob
Mühlmann, H. G.
Müller, Alfred
Muller, Franz J.
Müller, Hans
Müller, Hans Dieter
Müller, Joachim
Müller, Karl Alexander von
Müller, Nina
Müller, Otto Alexander von
Müller, Wilhelm Benedikt
Müller, Wolfgang
Muller-Hallwachs, Erica von
Müller-Kamp, Erich
Muller-Wirth, Robert
Mulsmann, Günther
Mummenhoff, Agnes
Münchner akademische Versangbuchhandlung
Münchener Arbeitskreis für Ostforschung
Münchner Uraufführungsbühne
Münchner Leben (Zellner, Werner)
Münchner Rundgespräch über die Hilfe für Heimatlose Ausländer
Münchner Verlag
Musik-Verlag Wilhelm Zimmermann
Musterschmidt Verlag
Mutterer, E.
Naef, Paul
Nägel, Klaus
Nassauische Landesbibliotheke
Nathusius, Hans
Naum, H. G.
Neander, G.
Neledinskii, Evgenii (Pseud. Evgenii Shugaev)
Nemitz, Fritz
Neske (Verlag Günther Neske Pfullingen)
Neuberger, Werner Der Neue Film Die Neue Furche Neue Gemeinschaft für Wohnkultur Neue literarische Welt Der Neue Tag Neue Verlags-Gesellschaft
Neumann, Franz
Neumann, Heinzgeorg
Nidda, R. Krug von
Niederhacke, Heinrich and Eva
Niederrheinische Verwaltungs- und Wirtschaftsakademie Duisburg
Niedermayr, Hans
Niederrheinische Verwaltungs- und Wirtschaftsakademie
Niemann, Karl-Heinz
Niemann, Ol'ga
Nishop, Hedwig
Nithardis, M.
Noack, Ulrich
Nocks, Wolfgang
Noeder, Ernst
Nordische Filmtage Lubeck 1964 (Hiller, Rolf)
Nordmann-Mörike, Katja
Nordmayer, Martin Nous. Internationale Zeitschrift für Wissenschaften Novosadov, Boris
Nowakowski, Tadeusz
Nunkesser, Clementine Nürnberger Nachrichten Nützmann, Karl
Ob"edinenie Rossiiskikh Studentov
Obermüller, H.
Obpacher Buch- und Kunstverlag München
Obrucheva, T.
Oebel, Hans Christoph
Oetken, ?
Ofrosimov, IUrii Viktorovich
Oldenburger Kunstverein
Olschki, Fernando
Oppenheim, Friedrich Carl
Organizatsionnoe Biuro po sozyvu Vsegermanskoi Konferentsii...Emigrantov iz SSSR
O'Rourke, Stephanie
Orthodox-Evangelische Studententagung in Marburg/Lahn
Ortsvereinigung Essen
Osé, Gisela (Mechke?)
Osten Sacken, Eveline
Österreichische Nationalbibliothek
Österreichischer Rundfunk
Österreichisches Komitee für internationalen Studienaustausch
Osteuropa Institut an der Universität Freiburg (Schweiz)
Osteuropaisches Arbeitskreis
Ost-Probleme. Redaktion
Ostwald, L.
Osval'd, Iuliia (J. Oswalt)
Oswald, Walter
Ott, Alfons
Ottenberg, Erma
Ottho, W.
Otto, Franz
Otto, Jens-Peter
Otto Falckenberg Schule
Otto Reichl Verlag
Ottow, Fred and Gerda
Overhoff, Julius
Overseas News Agency
Paasche, Manfred
Pabst, Valentin (Willibald Pirkheimer-Kuratorium)
Pädagogische Akademie
Pädagogische Hochschule Augsburg
Pädagogische Hochschule (Hannover)
Pahl, Helmut
Pakorch, H.
Palets, Lidiia
Palm, Alfred
Palombini, Freiherr von Paneuropa Panzer, Wolfgang and Martha
Papendick, V.
Pappenheim, Julie von (nee Rüdiger)
Parry-Hausenstein, Renée-Marie
Paul, Bernard
Paul, George (Zhorzh Pol')
Paul, Herbert
Paul Pattloch Verlag
Pauquit, P.
Pause, L.
Pavlov, [S.]
Pel' Gertruda Rudol'fovna
Peloux, I.
Pel'ttser, Elena
Penchershewsky, Alexander (Aleksandr Aleksandrovich Penkherzhevskii)
Perekrestnik, Vladimir Mikhailovich
Pereslavtsev, Evgenii (Eugene Perry)
Peschel, Tamara
Peterich, Magnus
Petersen, Jaspar
Petersilie, Eduard
Petersmann, Elvira
Petri, Harald
Petukhova, Vera Nikolaevna
Pfaller, Oscar
Pfeffer, Hanneli and Helmut
Pfeffermann, Karl Leonhard
Pfeiffer, Louis
Pfeiffer-Belli, Erich
Pföhler, N.
Pfeil, Peter Graf von
Pfister. Augsburger Waagenfabrik Ludwig Pfister
Pfister, B.
Pfister, Li
Pfizer, Theodor and Ursula
Pfleiderer, Otto
Pföhler, Nina Evgen'evna (Feler)
Pfuhle, Irene
Philippi, Hans
Phillipp, Werner
Phillips Universität (Slavisches Seminar; Studium Generale)
Philologisches Privat-Archiv Karl-Heinz Fleitmann
Philosophische-Theologische Hochschule Dillingen
Philosophische-Theologische Hochschule Freising
Philosophische-Theologische Hochschule Regensburg
Physikalisches Institut der Johannes Guttenberg-Universität
Physiologisches Institut Tierärztliche Hochschule
Physiologisches Institut (Heidelberg)
Pietzsch, Eva
Pikola, Rudolf
Pilger Verlag Speyer
Pimnenko, P.
Piper, Elisabeth
Piper, Martin
Piper, ?
Pistor
Pistusch, Eva
Pitusch (?), B.
Plachte, K.
Pleige, Barbara Rolsant
Plenius, Else
Podewils, Graf
Polcuch, Valentin
Polezhaev, N.
Polivanov, M. K.
Polutov, N.
Pomachanskii, M. (Protoierei)
Popliuiko, Nadezhda Anadosteeva and Anatolii
Postamt
Postel, Irmgard
Praelitz, Werner
Praetorius, Emil
Predigerseminar der Evangelischer Kirche in Rheinland
Preuves. Revue Mensuelle...
Pridsvet, I. and E.
Prigorowsky, Tania Prisma Prittwitz, H. I.
Prittwitz, M.
Prokoptschuk, G.
Pruspors, E.
Prutscher, Pius Michael
Przybylski, P. Lic.
Psychologisches Institut der Johannes Gutenberg-Universität
Publizistisches Büro und Verlag Dr. Paul Herzog
Puhris, Michael
Pursni, ?
Pusanov, B. and L.
Radecki, Gabriele von
Radio Stuttgart
Radke, Hans Dieter
Radtke-Frankenstein, Irmgard
Rafetzeder-Lach, Ursula
Ralfs, Günter
Rammelmeyer, A.
Ranitz, Ilse
Rausch, Carola
Reber, Robert
Rechel, Eva
Recklinghausen (City)
Redslob, Edwin
Regierungshauptkasse München
Regierungsrat
Regulenko, R.
Rehbach, A.
Reich, G.
Reichel, Marie Luis
Reimann, J. P.
Reimer, A.
Reimwald, ?
Reinbard, Luise Angela
Reinman, S. V.
Reiske, R.
Reisner, Erich
Rembrandt Verlag
Remmersen, D.
Remmert, Ruth
Remplein, Ellen
Rentschler, H.E.
Rentsler, Oscar
Repenak, G. and M.
Resler, Emmerich
Reuter, Rudolf
Revers, W. J.
Rhein-Ruhr-Klub
Riabikina, L.
Richard Pflaum Verlag
Richter, Erhard
Richter, Max
Richter, Peter and Adinda (Auer)
Richthofen, Baron von
Ricker, Gerhard
Rickert, Arnold
Rickert, Dorothea (Eder)
Rickert, Maria
Rickert, Sophie
Rider, Georgii Vladimirovich
Riechert, Johannes
Reidel, Claudia
Riedel, Kurt
Riedweg, Franz
Riedweg, Michael
Rieger, Elise and Rerta
Rieppel, Eva
Rieppel, Paul
Rietkötter, Karl
Rimscha, Hans v.
Ring christlich-demokratischer Studenten
Rinkel, Hans
Rintelin, ?
Rittersche Buch- und Kunsthandlung
Robert Wusterhausen Buchvertrieb
Rödling, Inge M.
Roepenack, Jenny (geb. Birkenfeldt)
Roesen, ?
Roh, Franz and Juliane
Röhling, Horst
Rolin, Aleksandr
Romezke, Gert
Röscheisen, Hans
Rosenberg, Alfons
Rosenberg, A.
Rösler, Elisabeth
Roslavleva, Vera
Rossiskoe Natsional'noe Ob"edinenie (N. Alimov)
Rost, H.
Rotenberger Volkshochschule
Roth, Maria
Rotherund ?, Elisabeth
Rothes, Wolfgang
Roth-Galitzine, Heinz and Helen (Galitsina Elena L'vovna)
Rothmund, Dr.
Roth-Seefrid, C.F.
Roubiczek, Paul
Rounalt, Jean
Rowohlt Verlag
Rübel, Elisabeth
Rubner, Heinrich
Rüchardt, Marie
Rüdel, Liane
Rüdiger, Rheinhold
Rudolf, Hildegart
Rudolph-Shabinsky, Vera
Rudolph-Steiner-Schulverein (München)
Ruediger, Dietrich
Rueff, M.
Rupegnel ?, K. H.
Ruhrmann, Manfred
Rupé, Karin
Ruperti, Boris
Ruperti, F.
Ruperti, I.
Ruprecht, Karl
Ruprecht-Karl-Universität Russland und Wir Rüttenauer, Isabella
Sachse und Hunselmann Saeculum. Jahrbuch für Universitätsgeschicte (G. Stadtmüller)
Saile, O.
Sailer-Riederer, Marietta
St. Michaelskirche
St. Petri-Domkirche (Bremen)
St. Willibrordsabdij (Gerhard Helwig)
Salin, Edgar
Saller, K.
Salzburg, G.
Sanatorium Quisisana
Sanneborn, Marlise
Sannikova, Natal'ia
Les Sans Bureau
Sapozhkov, A.
Sarnetzki, Othmar Heinrich
Sattler, D.
Saweljew, Aleksei and Margarita
Saxer, Melanie
Schab, Karl
Schabert, Otto
Schaefers, Pater Damianus
Schäfer, Amanda
Schäfer, Toni
Schäfer, ?
Schallweg, Paul
Scharl, Emmeran
Scharlau, Winfried
Scharnagl, Karl (Burgermeister der Landhapstadt)
Scharnhorst, Gundbert
Scharschuch, Dr.
Schattenmann, Johannes
Scheffel, Arvid V. (Sheffel')
Scheibert, Peter
Scheikel, Hans
Schelckberg, Vladimir Aleksandrovich
Schelung, A.
Schenk, Günther
Schenk, Hans Georg
Scherden, C.
Scherz und Goverts Verlag
Scheven, Ilsemarie
Schichler, Mechthild
Schidlowsky, P.
Schiessl, Sieglinde
Schiffers, Pfarrer
Schiller, Gertrud
Schilling, H.
Schilling, M. H.
Schimmelwitz-Hegmann, Charlotte
Schimmöller, H.
Schischkoff, Georgi
Schkurko, Victor (Viktor Petrovich Shkurko)
Schleim, ?
Schlemmer, Adolf (Privatklinik Dr. Schlemmer)
Schler, Georg
Schlesinger, F. (Shlezinger)
Schlintze, Hanna